Week 8. Day 1. Neat. Acronym. Employment. Refer to.
Psychological. Qualification. Economy. Fierce. Motivation. Vicious circle.
Perform. Index. Look forward to. Shame. Day 2. What are carbon offsets?
Offset. Scramble. Comply with. Obligation.
Protocol. Emission. Reduction. Entity. Carbon credit. Emit. Tap and force. Day 3.
Parasites. Parasite. Host. Shelter. Harmless. Bookworm. Intestine. Suck. Frightening.
Amoeba. Cavity. Dust mite. Eyelash. Starve. Blindness. Infection. Day 4. A mixed new world.
Mixed. Virtual. Resemble. Palace. Tricky. Shut out. Wrap. Background. Digital. Vast. Day 5.
The world's oldest sports. Cricket. Officially. Monastery. Entertainment. Racket. Evolve.
Establish. Score. Hip. Thigh. Day 6. Victorian art. Era. Outlook. Explosion. Consume. Pre-Raphaelite.
Composition. Explode with. Fascinate. Middle Ages. Monarch. Boundary.